reseze.net 2003-04-24

# ResEze - Policies

## policies  
  
**Our Secure Booking Guarantee**

ResEze.com is all about enabling you to feel comfortable when selecting and booking your lodging so that you can travel with confidence. The ResEze.com Secure Booking Guarantee protects you while you book reservations at ResEze.com, so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. 

We guarantee that every transaction you make at ResEze.com will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of making a reservation on ResEze.com. See guarantee details below. 

**Why is ResEze.com so safe?**

ResEze.com is powered by the ResEze booking engine. ResEze's secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure e-commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. In addition, ResEze.com only passes your information to our own secure servers, so that your personal information is safe throughout your visit to ResEze.com. 

You can take comfort in knowing that hundreds of thousands of customers have already safely booked their rooms on the ResEze.com system without credit card fraud or any other security problems. 

**Guarantee Details**

The ResEze.com Security Guarantee: You pay nothing if fraudulent charges are made as a result of booking at ResEze.com. 

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank generally cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, ResEze.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. ResEze.com will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from a booking made on ResEze.com while using our secure server. 

**ResEze.com Privacy Statement**

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected, and what organization is collecting the information, how the information is used and with whom the information may be shared. 
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 
  * What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control. 

RND Software Technology  Inc. is owner and operator of the ResEze.com Web site. RND Software Technology  Inc. and ResEze.com are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not and will not sell your personal information to anyone. This Web site has agreed to notify you of: 

**What personally identifiable information of yours is collected, what organization is collecting the information, how the information is used and with whom the information may be shared?**

ResEze.com is owned and operated by RND Software Technology  Inc. 

As you make reservations on the ResEze.com Web site, personal information such as your name, mailing address, daytime phone number and e-mail address are collected.

When you make a reservation on ResEze.com, your personal and credit card information are forwarded to the property in which you have reserved. The property will use this information to process your reservation. A representative of that property or a Customer Support representative of RND Software Technology Inc./ResEze.com may contact you if there is a question about your reservation. 

We share aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and reservations with our suppliers and partners, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. 

**We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.**

We will disclose individual personal information if we are subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law. 

Like most Web sites, there is certain information we automatically track, including the URL that you just came from, which URL you next go to, the browser you are using, and your IP address. 

We do NOT use cookies. 

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**

When you make a reservation on ResEze.com, your personal and credit card information are forwarded to the property in which you have reserved. The property will use this information to process your reservation. A representative of that property or a Customer Support representative of RND Software Technology Inc./ResEze.com may contact you if there is a question about your reservation. 

**What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company's control?**

When you make a new reservation or make changes to an existing reservation, we offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology encrypts all information you input before it is sent to our server. 

ResEze.com contains links to other sites. Any external links occurring on the ResEze.com Web site are provided for convenience and purely informational purposes. While we try to find sites that are of value to you, RND Software Technology  Inc. cannot be held responsible for any content, political views or endorsements that may be found in any of our external links. RND Software Technology  Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

All content and photos on our property pages are provided directly by the properties for your convenience and information. RND Software Technology  Inc. will not be held responsible for any inability to access any content on these pages or any inaccuracies or discrepancies that may occur on property pages. 

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or would like more information about our company, please contact us: 

RND Software Technology Inc.  
[info@rndsti.com  
](mailto:info@rndsti.com)
